const questionsObj = {
    questionsArray: [
        {
            id: 0,
            quizTitle: 'Quiz Title 1',
            quizBrief: 'Something about quiz 1',
            questions: [
                {
                    question: 'This is the first question.',
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 1',
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the second question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 2'
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the third question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 3'
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the fourth question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 4',
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the fifth question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 2'
                },
            ],
        },
        {
            id: 1,
            quizTitle: 'Quiz Title 2',
            quizBrief: 'Something about quiz 2',
            questions: [
                {
                    question: 'This is the first question.',
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 1',
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the second question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 2'
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the third question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 3'
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the fourth question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 4'
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the fifth question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 4'
                },
            ],
        },
        {
            id: 2,
            quizTitle: 'Quiz Title 3',
            quizBrief: 'Something about quiz 3',
            questions: [
                {
                    question: 'This is the first question.',
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 1',
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the second question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 2'
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the third question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 3'
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the fourth question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 4'
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the fifth question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 4'
                },
            ],
        },
        {
            id: 3,
            quizTitle: 'Quiz Title 4',
            quizBrief: 'Something about quiz 4',
            questions: [
                {
                    question: 'This is the first question.',
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 1',
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the second question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 2'
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the third question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 3'
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the fourth question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 4'
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the fifth question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 4'
                },
            ],
        },
        {
            id: 4,
            quizTitle: 'Quiz Title 5',
            quizBrief: 'Something about quiz 5',
            questions: [
                {
                    question: 'This is the first question.',
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 1',
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the second question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 2'
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the third question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 3'
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the fourth question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 4'
                },
                {
                    question: "This is the fifth question.",
                    options: [
                        'This is option 1',
                        'This is option 2',
                        'This is option 3',
                        'This is option 4',
                    ],
                    answer: 'This is option 4'
                },
            ],
        }
    ]
};

export { questionsObj }